(Bernadette:)What difference
does it make?
(Howard:)I don't know.
I was hoping some poor kid
(Howard:)would come up to me and say,
(high-pitched British accent):
Please, sir, I want some more.
(Raj:)You're in a soup kitchen,
(Raj:)not a production
of Oliver!
(Howard:)It's not like
I'm expecting them to sing.
(Sheldon:)...and then the next day
was 73 degrees,
(Sheldon:)and the day after that
was 72,
(Sheldon:)and then it was
72 again...
(Sheldon:)uh, then it was 74,
(Sheldon:)and that brings us
to today, at...
(Sheldon:)I'd wear shorts
if I had a pair... 78.
(Amy:)Are we done discussing
the weather?
(Sheldon:)I don't know if
I'd call it "discussing."
(Sheldon:)You kind of sat back
and let me do all the work.
(Sheldon:)Let's see
(Sheldon:)what's next on the list.
Oh, here.
Uh, "Do you whittle,
"and if so, what kind of knife
do you..."
Sheldon.
(Amy:)We've known each other
a long time.
(Amy:)We are perfectly capable
of having a conversation
(Amy:)without relying on a list
off the Internet.